4 portfolios sorted by size and by illiquidity

Daily Returns: from February 1, 2001.

Every month t, we double-sort (ascending) the eligible stocks (as defined below) according to their market capitalization in month t-1 and and the previous twelve month moving average of illiquidity, built as in Amihud (2002), with median breakpoint for each variable (2x2). We then hold the portfolios during month t.

For each portfolio we provide the following time series: Equally Weighted Return and Value Weighted Return.

The Eligibility Criteria

A stock traded in BOVESPA is considered “eligible” for year t if it meets 3 criteria:
- The stock is the most traded stock of the firm (the one with the highest traded volume during last year);

- The stock was traded in more than 80% of the days in year t-1 with volume greater than R$ 500.000,00 per day. In case the stock was listed in year t-1, the period considered
goes from the listing day to the last day of the year;

- The stock was initially listed prior to December of year t-1.